[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A major earthquake struck this city in 1906, killing almost 3,000 people.", "correct_answer": "San Francisco", "incorrect_answers": ["Taipei", "Wellington", "Tokyo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Catcher Jake Taylor, played by Tom Berenger in Major League, was a former All Star for what Major League team according to team management?", "correct_answer": "Boston Red Sox", "incorrect_answers": ["Chicago White Sox", "New York Yankees", "Cleveland Indians"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many times does Hoosiers character Coach Dale tell his players they must pass before shooting?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["0", "5", "2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Dutch naval officer, who became a folk hero during the Eighty Years War between the Dutch republic and Spain, sailed out to capture the Spanish treasure fleet in 1628.", "correct_answer": "Pieter Heyn", "incorrect_answers": ["Heindrich Van Duten", "Henry Hudson", "Petyr Stuvessant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name of which country is derived from the Latin word for silver?", "correct_answer": "Argentina", "incorrect_answers": ["Ecuador", "El Salvador", "Albania"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I am someone else when Im with you, someone more like myself. (2001)", "correct_answer": "Original Sin", "incorrect_answers": ["Sunrise: A Song of Two Humans", "Trouble in Paradise", "In America"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How does Princess Fionas mother Queen Lillian break a hole into the wall of the dungeon in the movie Shrek the Third?", "correct_answer": "With her head", "incorrect_answers": ["By hitting a very high note", "With dynamite", "With magic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these in NOT a species of raccoon?", "correct_answer": "Tree Raccoon", "incorrect_answers": ["Common Raccoon", "Tres Marias Raccoon", "Crab Eating Raccoon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The proteins in dead organisms as well as in body wastes are converted into ammonia by bacteria and fungi. Into what useful product do other bacteria convert this ammonia?", "correct_answer": "Nitrates", "incorrect_answers": ["Phosphoric acid", "Amino acids", "Polypeptides"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first Bulgarian state was formed in this year.", "correct_answer": "681 AD", "incorrect_answers": ["429 AD", "712 AD", "651 AD"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is the ninth Sign of the Chinese Zodiac.  It is best described as this.", "correct_answer": "Active and Agile", "incorrect_answers": ["Powerful", "Soft and Fentle", "Steady  Persistent"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What album is considered to be the first rap record?", "correct_answer": "Sugar Hill Gangss Rappers Delight", "incorrect_answers": ["Public Enemys Fight the Power", "Ike Turners Jet  88", "Yannick Bruynoghes Big Bills Rap"]}]